http://www.huntingtontheatre.org/privacy-policy/

Now on sale >
Raise the CurtainCharles Dickens' A Christmas CarolDream Boston Huntington @ HomeSchool Registration
2020-2021 seasonSubscribe >
Benefits & ExtrasPackages & Prices
CalendarComplete Your Experience >
Post-Show ConversationsHumanities ForumsActors Forums35 Below
New Play Development >
Breaking Ground FestivalPlaywright-In-ResidenceHuntington Playwriting FellowsSummer WorkshopCommissionsPlay Submission Information
Plan Your Visit
COVID-19 & PUBLIC HEALTH UPDATETicketing Services Information >
Ticketing Services HoursTicket Prices & SeatingHuntington Community Membership InitiativeDiscount Ticket ProgramsGroup Sales
About Us
Our MissionAnti-Racism Public UpdateWho's WhoThe New Huntington: Building Boston's Creative HubProduction HistoryGet Involved >
Venue Rentals >
Huntington Avenue TheatreCalderwood Pavilion at the BCA BCA Plaza Theatres
PartnersBest of Boston 20192013 Regional Tony AwardContact Us
Education
Huntington @ HomeSchoolStudent MatineesDramatic Returns Student Programs >
Poetry Out Loud MassachusettsAugust Wilson Monologue CompetitionCodman Academy Charter Public School PartnershipEPIC: Empowered Performers in Conversation
Curriculum GuidesMeet the Education DepartmentVideos & More
Support Us
Make A GiftWays To GiveDonor BenefitsLegacy GivingCorporate, Foundation & Government GivingJoin The HuntThe New Huntington: Building Boston's Creative HubSpotlight Gala
MENU
Login
Logout
Cart
Plays & Events
Now on sale
2020-2021 season
Subscribe
Learn More
Did you know?
Over the past 30 years, over 3.5 million patrons have seen a show at the Huntington!
Buy Tickets Subscribe Donate
Privacy Policy
This is the website of the Huntington Theatre Company. Our postal address is: Huntington Theatre Company 264 Huntington Avenue Boston, MA 02115-4606
We can be reached via email at thehuntington@huntingtontheatre.org,			or you can call our administrative office at 617 266 7900.
The Information We Collect and How We Use It
Information Provided by You
How We Use Your Information
Security of Your Information
Disclaimers
Links to Third Party Sites
IP Address
Cookies
Correcting or Updating Personal Information
Your Acceptance of These Terms
The Information We Collect and How We Use It We collect information on the site in order to make it possible for you to access all the features on our site and to enhance your overall experience on our site. You can browse our site without submitting any personally identifiable information, but we do collect some anonymous information when you access our site. We also collect information volunteered by our patrons, such as survey information and/or site registrations.
back to top
Information Provided by You When you visit our site, you will be invited to register in order to access some of our services. When you register, you will be asked to provide some personal information, including your name and email address. You may also purchase subscriptions or single tickets, and/or make donations on the Huntington website, where you will be asked for your billing and/or mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and expiration date so that we can process your purchase.
back to top
How We Use Your Information Patrons who have completed a subscription, single ticket, or donation transaction online and have supplied us with their address may receive periodic mailings from the Huntington Theatre Company with information on new productions, discount offers, or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings‚ please let us know by emailing us at thehuntington@huntingtontheatre.org. You may also receive mailings from other local arts organizations and not-for-profit companies. You can‚ however‚ have your name put on our do-not-share list by emailing us at thehuntington@huntingtontheatre.org. Please provide us with your exact name and mailing address in the e-mail‚ and we will be sure to remove your name from the list that we share with other organizations.
Patrons who have completed a subscription, single ticket, or donation transaction online and have supplied us with their telephone number may receive telephone calls from the Huntington Theatre Company with information on new productions, discount offers, or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls‚ please let us know by emailing us at thehuntington@huntingtontheatre.org. You may also receive telephone calls from select local arts organizations. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by emailing us at thehuntington@huntingtontheatre.org. Please provide us with your name and phone number, and we will be sure to remove your name from the list we share with other organizations.
If you create an account at HuntingtonTheatre.org, the Huntington Theatre Company may also use your contact information to send you email about new offerings and special theatre-related events that may be of interest to you. Please note that the Huntington will never, ever trade, rent, or sell your email address to anyone. If you do not want to receive email from the Huntington Theatre Company in the future‚ please let us know by sending an email to thehuntington@huntingtontheatre.org and providing us with your name and email address.
back to top
Security of Your Information When you purchase a subscription or single ticket or make a donation, we need to obtain your credit card number, expiration date, and billing address information. This information is encrypted and transmitted over the Internet where it is stored securely, and used for billing purposes only. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
back to top
Disclaimers The Huntington Theatre Company exercises reasonable care in mitigating any potential issues associated with the operation of our website, including, but not limited to, utilizing security software applications and employing computer consultants. We realize, however, that a multitude of technical issues can arise in our website operations.
To this effect, the Huntington Theatre Company does not warrant that the functions contained on this website will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that our web pages or ISP or server operations that host or transmit any webpage or content contained thereon is free of viruses or other harmful defects.
In the event that there exists a conflict between posted materials, policies, or any other terms on the website and any executed agreements, such as subscription policies, donor agreements, or any other arrangements, the executed agreement and its terms will prevail and will be given full force and effect with modification.
The Huntington Theatre Company's website and its materials are provided on an "AS IS" basis without any kind of warranties or representations, either express or implied, regarding, among other things, the accuracy, completeness, or reliability of text, graphics, opinions, and other items accessed from or via this website.
The Huntington Theatre Company, its suppliers, or any other third parties mentioned on this website shall not be liable, under any circumstances, for direct, indirect, incidental, special, or consequential damagers, including, but not limited to, costs associated with servicing, repairing, and/or replacing equipment, lost data, lost profits, or business interruptions, resulting from the use or inability to use this website and its materials, whether or not the Huntington is advised of the possibility of such damages.
back to top
Links to Third Party Sites This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that the Huntington Theatre Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement policy applies solely to information collected by this website.
back to top
IP Address We automatically track IP (internet protocol) addresses for statistic purposes. IP addresses are logged per user's session and help to determine how often areas on our site are visited. The Huntington does not track IP addresses with any of your personal information, so we will never link an IP address to a specific user. We also monitor traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop and improve the design and layout of the site.
back to top
Cookies We use cookies to improve your experience at HuntingtonTheatre.org. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. We use cookies for remarketing and to remember information users give us so they don't have to reenter it each time they visit our site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits. Even without a cookie, you will still be able to use most of the features on our site.
back to top
Correcting or Updating Personal Information If your personal information changes, we will gladly correct, update, or remove any data you have previously provided to us. You may change your personal information at any time by sending an email to thehuntington@huntingtontheatre.org. We may retain a copy of the prior version for our records.
back to top
Your Acceptance of These Terms By visiting HuntingtonTheatre.org, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We will always fully disclose our privacy policies, and if our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.
If you choose to visit HuntingtonTheatre.org, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy.
back to top
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may e-mail us at thehuntington@huntingtontheatre.org.
Thank you for your interest in the Huntington Theatre Company.
Avenue of the Arts / Huntington Avenue Theatre: 264 Huntington Avenue, Boston MA 02115South End / Calderwood Pavilion at the BCA: 527 Tremont Street, Boston MA 02116Main: 264 Huntington Avenue, Boston MA 02115 | 617 266 7900 |TICKETING SERVICES 617 266 0800
Login
Update Account
Contact
Privacy Policy
FAQ
Site Map
© 2020 Huntington Theatre Company. All rights reserved | Trouble viewing this site? Please download Mozilla Firefox or Google Chrome.
